DAVID BALDUS PAPERS (APAP329) 1965-2011
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Pennsylvania Research, 1992-2011; 11; 40.5
  - Miller-El Research, 1997-2011; 11.5; 3
    - Correspondence- Robert Dunham, article on Miller-El and Philadelphia Batson cases, 2010 October 22-23 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Call for Papers, Batson v. Kentucky Symposium, ca. 2010 December (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Batson v. Kentucky Symposium, 2011 February 6 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence- Research Assistant MB, organization of Batson cases, 2011 May 31 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence- Research on Philadelphia Batson cases, 2011 April 13 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Research Assistant MB Batson case summaries A-B, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Research Assistant MB Batson case summaries C-H, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Research Assistant MB Batson case summaries J-U, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Brief- Thomas Miller El v. Douglas Dretke, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Case Summaries and briefs- 3rd Circuit Pennsylvania Batson cases, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Draft- "Statistical Proof of Swain and Batson Claims of Discrimination in the Use of Peremptory Challenges: Reflections on Principles of Research Design, Data Base Construction, and Statistical interpretation", Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Literature- Batson Proof, Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Literature- Materials returned from Research Assistant MB, Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Literature- Pre- Batson and Part- Batson cases, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Miller-El v. Cockrell, Clarence Thomas and Antonin Scalia opinions, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Notes, Drafts- Tables 6 and 7, Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Research Assistant Batson Empirical Analysis, Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Research Assistant Summaries on Miller-El cases, Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Research Assistant Summaries on Miller-El cases, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Research Assistant Summaries on Miller-El cases, Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Swain v. Alabama Decision, Undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Transcript of Jack McMoahon Training tape, Undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Material form the Defenders' Association of Philadelphia, 1985-2008; 12; 84.7
  This series contains the Charging and Sentencing Study Case Files for both Pennsylvania and Philadelphia, the Data Collection Instruments, the Severity Study, the Venire Study, and the Subject Files.
  - Charging and Sentencing Study Pennsylvania Case Files, 1985-2000; 12.1; 17.4
    The series is arranged alphabetically by last name.
    The series contains the Charging and Sentencing Study of Pennsylvania case files by defendant's last name.
    - Seifullah Abdul-Sala - Cumberland, 941499, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Mark Abrial - Bucks, 17381983, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Charles Adams - Fayette, 4882, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Leonard E. Aiken - Erie, 128685, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Aldred Albrecht - Bucks, 40891980, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Billy Allen - Montgomery, 5002, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - David Allen - Clarion, 291984, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Todd Allen - Allegheny, 7906703, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Roland Alston - Bucks, 30041983 [1 of 2], 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Roland Alston - Bucks, 30041983 [2 of 2], 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Albert Altimari - Bucks, 43100186 [1 of 2], 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Albert Altimari - Bucks, 43100186 [2 of 2], 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Robert Altland - York, 3661979, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Miguel Alvarez - Montgomery, 65181989, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Roberto Alvarez - Montgomery, 65181989, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Michael Anderson - Allegheny, 8912989, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - John Annarino - Allegheny, 18209217, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Robert Amok - Lancaster, 17001985, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Martin Appel - Northhampton, 10761986, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Frederic Arelt - Allegheny, 8100941, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Harold Arndt - Lancaster, 1101990, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Dale Arnold - Bradford, 801026, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Allen Artz - Berks, 178284, Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Robert Auker - Northumberland, 91298, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Joseph Alisio - Lackawanna, 811386, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Grace Azzarella - Cambria, 8171980, Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Orlando Baez - Lancaster, 9381992, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Maurice Bailey - Allegheny, 9314654, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Bruce Bainbridge - Schuylkill, 41979, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Christop Baker - Potter, 1191992, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Eugene Banks - Bucks, 30831982 [1 of 2], Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Eugene Banks - Bucks, 30831982 [2 of 2], Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Walter Baker - Montgomery, 684592, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - John Banis - Luzerine, 1456198, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - George Banks - Luzerine, 150682, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Leroy Banks - York, 3251982, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Fredrick Banner - Lehigh,12901989, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Michael Brado - Luzerine, 27781992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Harry Barnes - Lawrence, 9151990, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Daniel Barnett - Chester, 7311990, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Gilberto Barreto - Berks, 81036201, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Angelo Barret - Beaver, 731988, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Kevin Barron - Lehigh, 13511983, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Norman Batson - Allegheny, 8706814, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - William Beam - Beaver, 8971989, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Richard Beasly - Allegheny, 8709310, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Ralph Beck - Dauphin, 13411980, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Charles Bechtel - Perry, 81990, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Earmon Beck - Allegheny, 8201287, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Warren Beckman - Cumberland, 8961981, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Nicolas Belgiorno - Deleware, 511987, Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Brian Bedsoul - York, 36171990, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - James begley - York, 1752CA19, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Michael Bell - Erie, 351A1996, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Marco Benitez - Dauphin, 23311983, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Edward Bennet - Allegheny, 8506282, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Krik Bennet - Dauphin, 4431980, Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Dennis Benson - Elk, 3819, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Todd Bercaw - Northampton, 9911992 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Cyd Berger - Allegheny, 8008057, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - William berry - Allegheny, 9004698, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Guy Bicking - Lackawanna, 87208, Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Robert Billings - Jefferson, 2501986, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Christopher Bissey - Northampton, 2901996, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Robert Bittinger - Dauphin, 5201985, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Steven Bleau - Chester, 4431988, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Paul bloom - Dauphin, 99001983, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Scott Blystone - Fayette, 21984, Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Leonard Bocchicchio - Blair, 48682, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Christopher Bocelli - Chester, 40641990, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Michael Boettlin - Berks, 871853, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Anthony Boggs - Chester, 50597, Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Ralph Bolden - Allegheny, 9500193, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Terry Boles - Franklin, 181984, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Robert Boring - Blair, 94CR462, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Thomas Bonner - Montgomery, 49001985, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Alan Borger - Lehigh, 711991, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Colin Bortz - Westmoreland, 152C1994 [1 of 2], 1995 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Colin Bortz - Westmoreland, 152C1994 [2 of 2], 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Otis Boyd - Allegheny, 9101335, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - James A.Boyer - Centre, 1993856 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - William Bradfield - Dauphin, 9081983, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Terrence Bradley - Allegheny, 8906702, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Richard Brant - Allegheny, 8102721, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Mark Breakiron - Fayette, 33187, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Michael Breidenstein - Berks, 821275, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Robert Bricker - Allegheny, 8104233, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Robert Briker - Allegheny, 8104541, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Robert Briker - Allegheny, 8104541, Second case, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Shawnfatee Bridges - Berks, 11797, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Bennie Brimage - Allegheny, 7903213, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Charles Brobst - Luzerine, 13541990, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Richard Brode - Lebnanon, 8610889, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Antuan Bronshtein - Montgomery, 032793, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Purcell Bronson - Allegheny, 9308963, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - John Brookins - Bucks, 50601991, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Theodre Brosius - Northampton, 1841983, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - James Brough - Allegheny, 8910787, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - James Brown - Chester, 228086, Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Debra Brown - Butler, 2621984, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Raymond Brown - Allegheny, 9213785, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Charles Browning - Bucks, 61161991, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Kenneth Brown - Monroe, 1163-94, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Scott Burner - Blair, 83472, Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Robert Bryant - Allegheny, 8407686, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Roger Buehl - Montgomery, 30001982, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Robert Buli - Bucks, 28721978, Undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Edward Bungo - Luzerne, 461989, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Jerry Burgos - Monroe, 3061998, Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Jerry Burgos - Monroe, 3061988, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - James Burke - Berk, 32541990, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Dewitt Butler - Dauphin, 23361988, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - James Button - Tioga, 6782, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Roger Button - Tioga, 7782, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Roger Button - Tioga, 7782, Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - James Button - Tioga, 6782, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Anderw Byrne - Chester, 325691, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Wilfredo Caballero - York, 7271989, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Larry Cain - Dauphin, 219983, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Christop Caldwell - Allegheny, 8501202, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - John Calvaresi - Berks, 185487, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Otis Campbell - Allegheny, 9415246, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Emanual Campisi - Monroe, 6687, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Ricardo Campos - Deleware, 146193, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Vincent Caracciolo - Cambria, 5751983, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - John Caramadre - Cambria, 5771983, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Patricia Carbone - Somerset, 2781984, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - James Carpenter - York, 20141983, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Stephen Carr - Adams, 38588, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Victoria Cartagena - Northampton, 2951986, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Darryl Carter - Berks, 871177, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - David Carter - Allegheny, 8509897, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Alberto Castillo - Lehigh, 65091984, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Anthony Cessna - Lebanon, 6571985, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Terry Chamberlain - Bradford, 93CR000226, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Karl Chambers - York, 421987, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Edward Chaparro - Luzerne, 5121985, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Frank Chester - Bucks, 7411988 [1 of 2], 1996 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Frank Chester - Bucks, 7411988 [2 of 2], 1996 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - David Chmiel - Lackawanna, 83748, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - David Chimel - Lackawanna, 83748, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Russell Christopher - Fayette, 7811993, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Lawrence Christy - Cambria, 2701983, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Lawrence Church - Dauphin, 7851991, Undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Jeffrey Clapsadl - Berks, 236294, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Andre clark - Lancaster, 4841991, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Rashad Clark - Allegheny, 9401016, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Vander Clayborne - Delaware, 969690, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Jeffrey Clever - Franklin, 1771979, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Yvonne Cloud - Deleware, 314383, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - George Cobbs - Allegheny, 7902962, Undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - George Cobbs - Allegheny, 7902915, Undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - John Cohen - Mercer, 321987, Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Alan Cohick - Cumberland, 9231985, Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Clarence Coleman - Allegheny, 8707562, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Carlos Colon - Lancaster, 6521988, Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Martin Colson - Bucks, 22711980, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Kevin Colzie - Deleware, 261682, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Geroge Conrad - Perry, 1131981, Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Michael Conforti - Wayne, 641991, Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - James Convers - Dauphin, 8081989, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Samuel Contakos - Fayette, 8141978, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Tommy Copeland - Allegheny, 18100942, Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - David Copenhefer - Erie, 13251988, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Dennis Counterman - Lehigh, 250088, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Willard Cooper - Deleware, 245479, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Walter Cowfer - Butler, 8161990, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Willie Craig - Deleware, 393081, Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Jerome Cramer - Blair, [No Case#], Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Sherman Craver - Deleware, 190293, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Kevin Crawford - Berks, 32551990, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Paul Crews - Perry, 3181990, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Daniel Crispell - Clearfield, 9062, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - David Croll - Lehigh, 11987, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Melvin Cromedy - Lancaster, 14451988, Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Charles Cross - Beaver, 56581, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Abraham Cruz - Dauphin, 4061990, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - James Cruz - Centre, 19931246, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Ricardo Cruz - Lancaster, 11731992, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Willliam Curley - Bradford, 95CR0003, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Michael Dann - Erie, 3831992, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Sean Darrington - Dauphin, 2322CD1993, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Craig Datesman - Bucks, 40431982, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - David Davis - Lackawanna, 801328, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Allen Davis - Northampton, 3261981, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Glenn Davis - Tioga, 11CA92, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Joel Davis - Jefferson, 2281991, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - John Davis - Delaware, 32380, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Mark Davis - [No County], [No Case#], 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Scott Davis - York, 7281980, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Michael Dean - Lehigh, 2581983, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Ronald Debiak - Allegheny, 9006186, Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Jeffrey Deblase - Montgomery, 234885, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Thomas Deblase - Montgomery, 234985, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Charles Deblois - York, 5061981, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Eric Decker - Bucks, 28211980, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Robert Dehart - Huntingdon, 1441983, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Reynaldo DeJesus - Chester, 253785, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Vincent Delacerna - Allegheny, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Lawrence Delestienne - Cambria, 3951984, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Henry Dennison - Dauphin, 19481992, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Colson Derby - Bucks, 35241994, Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Steven Derk - Snyder, 1531992, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Phillip Devenshire - Cumberland, 15021992, Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Willie Dickson - York, 21801983, Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Eugene Dietz - Berks, 11181987, Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Theodore Dipretoro - Deleware, 438182, Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - John Dolene - Allegheny, 8101851, Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Edward Domes - Allegheny, 9308386, Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Steven Donbach - Dauphin, 31391988, Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Joseph Donnelly - Lancaster, 34801993, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Robert Dorler - Erie, 108919, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Miles Doss - Delaware, 578382, Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Louis Dottle - Lawrence, 2301990 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Scott Dougherty - Lackawanna, 74084, Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - David Drasher - Luzerne, 14111988, Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Steven Duffey - Lackawanna, 84176, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Steven Dunn - Luzerne, 1461990, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Trazis Durham - Beaver, 137496, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Joseph Dyson - Bucks, 59361992, Undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Anthony Eberhardt - Allegheny, 8004536, Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Gregory Eckert - Berks, 20881987, Undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Robert Eckert - Schuykill, 7871989, Undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Stephen Edmiston - Cambria, 102588, Undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - George Edwards - Lackawanna, 84529, Undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Jeffery Emerson - Chester, 16391989, Undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Thomas Epps - Dauphin, 7271980, Undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - David Ewing - Lancaster, 20521993, Undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Leroy Evans - Delaware, 300281, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Dorothy Farbo - Cambria, 2351992, Undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Arthur Faulkner - Montgomery, 31621988, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - James Favinger - Berks, 31761989, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Leroy Fears - Allegheny, 9408705, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Joseph Feliciano - Lehigh, 23621992, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Bernard Ferguson - Chester, 315287, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Anthony Ferraro - Allegheny, 8107528, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Brian Ferrebee - York, 23251989, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Frank Ferrera - Columbia, 1831990, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Francis Ferri - Allegheny, 8307144, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Robert Fisher - Montgomery, 113488, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Robert Fisher - Montgomery, 113488, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Johnny Fitzpatrick - Bucks, 17041991, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Gary Fitzsimmons - Bucks, 17251989, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Dennis Flanagan - Bucks, 28311981, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Jesus Flores - Lehigh, 3666199, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Domenic Florio - Deleware, 707582, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Melody Ford - Allegheny, 9015067, Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Andre Foreman - Montgomery, 436194 [1 of 2], 1995 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Andre Foreman - Montgomery, 436194 [2 of 2], 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Joseph Foreman - Bucks, 29351982, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Roy Fortune - Northumberland, 79223, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Michael Eoust - Venango, CR6791993, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Harry Fox - Dauphin, 5111984, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Stacey Fox - Lancaster, 51979, Undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Thosmas Fox - Luzerne, 1221990, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Gary Frame - Erie, 94986, Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Chad Franciscus - Chester, 468491, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Samuel Frank - Columbia, 1361989, Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Joseph Frankenberry - Fayette, 8112158, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Edward Fredrick - McKean, 1631982, Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - James Frey - York, 2819ACA19, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Roderic Frey - Lancastrer, 1691980, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Donald Fultz - Erie, 121788, Undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Miles Gabler - Allegheny, 8104539, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Tammy Gallagher - Allegheny, 820063, Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Richard Gallippi - Allegheny, 8601708, Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Jack Gallup - [No County], 4331992, Undated (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Gene Gash - Dauphin, 24311990, Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Jamil Gandy - Delaware, 645684, Undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Jose Garcia - Delaware, 32699, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Patric Gardner - Tioga, 112CA92, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Steven Gardner - Butler, CA2191995, Undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - David Garnett - Deleware, 461193, Undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - James Garnett - York, 1341989, Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Irvin Gass - Crawford, 47478, Undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Claude Gaston - Allegheny, CC9413639, Undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - James Gault - Westmoreland, 55884, Undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Percy Gavin - Erie, 2241990, Undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Maurice Gease - Deleware, 90294, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Kenneth Gerhard - Fayette, 3271985, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Robert Geyer- York, 24311990, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Barry Gibbs - Pike, 891984, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Jerome Gibson - Bucks, 511994, (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Jerome Gibson - Bucks, 511994, (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Michael Glass - Philadelphia, 93061625, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - William Gnecco - Bucks, 41591986, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Cynthia Gonzalez - Dauphin, 17991984, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Roberto Gonzalez - Berks, 31071989, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Thomas Garby - washington, 5551986, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Bernie Graves - Allegheny, 7901311, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Guy Grazier - Allegheny, 8800838, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Mark Graber - Bucks, 14091990, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Samuel Green - Northhampton, 2381988, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Freddie Greene - Lehigh, 2231979, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Thomas Greene - Bucks, 50791990, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Wallace Gribus - Crawford, 1984371 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - James griffin - Allegheny, 8104233, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Rodney Griffin - Delaware, 165584, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - James Grimes - Northhampton, 10451982 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Mark Grimm - Westmore Land, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Ellswort Groff - Lancaster, 9111983, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Jessie Grove - chester, 213781, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Paul Guglielmi - Montogomery, 45291985, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Norman Gundrum - Northumberland, CR944, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Mark Guy - Delaware, 11731991, Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Richard Guy - Allegheny, 8201794, Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Randy Haag - Berks, 84183501, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Larry Hake - York, 4121982, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Darrick Hall - Chester, 2994 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Earl Hall - Bradford, 842573, Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - George Halter - Allegheny, 8304748, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Michael Hamburger - Bucks, 45681981, Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Timothy Hanson - Clearfield, 87915, Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - James Hardin - Beaver, 10151989, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - James Hardin - Allegheny, 8701567, Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Eddie Hardison - Dauphin, 14531979, Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Willie Hardy - Erie, 16471993, Undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Francis Harris - Lancaster, 0672199, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Harry Beckett - Dauphin, 33931991, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Thomas Harris - Allegheny, 8105172, Undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Edward Harter - Clinton, 2080, Undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Robert Hartman - Westmoreland, 10891982, Undated (Box 7, Folder 43)